What
Figured it out
Take your stuff
Lewes
Just you wait
The secret feed
I must get my hands on it
If you don't give it to me
I have my own ways
I'll steal it if I have to
Lewes
Just you wait
I won't give up
Braised pork and big hock
Two meats and two veggies every day
The meals from Boss Lewes
In my ten-plus years of working
Are the best I've ever had
Not only is the food good
The pay is the highest too
Other places pay 3000
a month at most
Excluding benefits
We take home 6000
We gotta work hard
Exactly
Last month my mom fell
and was hospitalized
Without a second thought
The boss advanced me
three months' salary
Otherwise I couldn't afford
the medical bills
Our boss is the man
You're really sharp Jason
So many ingredients and ratios
You can remember them all
No wonder the boss put you
in charge of mixing
If I didn't have the skills
Would he pay me 10k
Do you really know Lewes's feed ratio